https://www.onlinembatoday.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to content Skip to primary sidebarHome
Rankings
Interviews
News
About
Quick Degree FinderSelect a Degree LevelSelect a DegreeAssociate'sBachelor'sMaster'sDoctorateNon-Degree CoursesCertificate / DiplomaGraduate CertificatesSelect a CategorySelect a CategoryArt & DesignBusiness & ManagementComputers & TechnologyCriminal Justice & LegalEducation & TeachingLiberal Arts & HumanitiesNursing & HealthcarePsychology & CounselingScience & EngineeringTrades & CareersSelect a SubjectSelect a SubjectAnimationArt & Art HistoryCreative / DesignFashionFilmGame DesignGraphic DesignInterior DesignLandscape ArchitectureMultimedia DesignPhotographyVisual CommunicationsWeb DesignAccountingBusiness AdministrationBusiness IntelligenceEconomicsEntertainment ManagementEntrepreneurshipFinanceForensic AccountingHospitality ManagementHotel & Restaurant ManagementHuman ResourcesInternational BusinessInternet MarketingLogisticsManagementManagement Information SystemsMarketingNon-Profit ManagementOrganizational LeadershipProject ManagementPublic RelationsReal EstateRetail & Sales ManagementRisk ManagementSmall BusinessSports ManagementSupply Chain & LogisticsTaxationTraining & DevelopmentComputer EngineeringComputer ForensicsComputer ProgrammingComputer ScienceDatabase ManagementInformation Systems SecurityInformation TechnologyInternet SecurityMobile DevelopmentNetwork AdministrationNetwork SecuritySoftware EngineeringWeb DevelopmentCorrectionsCrime Scene InvestigationCriminal JusticeCriminologyCyber SecurityForensic ScienceHomeland SecurityLaw EnforcementLegal StudiesParalegalPublic Safety AdministrationAdult Education/LearningChild DevelopmentCoachingCurriculum & InstructionEarly Childhood EducationEducationEducational AdministrationEducational CounselingEducational LeadershipEducational TechnologyElementary EducationEnglish Language LearningHigher EducationK-12 EducationLibrary ScienceMath EducationMusic EducationOnline TeachingReading & LiteracySpecial EducationTeacher LicensureAnthropologyCommunicationsEnglishGeneral StudiesGeographyHistoryHuman & Family DevelopmentJournalismLiberal ArtsMedia CommunicationsMinistryMusicPolitical SciencePublic AdministrationPublic PolicySocial ScienceSocial WorkSociologyTheologyWritingDental AssistanceEmergency ManagementGerontologyHealth EducationHealth InformaticsHealth ScienceHealth ServicesHealthcare AdministrationHealthcare ManagementHuman ServicesMedical AssistingMedical CodingMedical Office AdministrationNurse Practitioner (RN Required)Nursing (RN required)Nursing Education (RN Required)Nutritional SciencesPharmacyPublic HealthRN to BSN (RN required)Sports MedicineSports Medicine/Physical TherapyVeterinaryX-Ray TechnicianAddictions & RecoveryBehavioral PsychologyChild and Adolescent PsychologyCounselingEducational PsychologyFamily CounselingForensic PsychologyOrganizational PsychologyPsychologyAeronautics/AviationBiomedical EngineeringCivil EngineeringDraftingElectronics EngineeringEngineeringEngineering ManagementEnvironmental ManagementEnvironmental ScienceIndustrial EngineeringMechanical EngineeringAutomotiveCarpentryConstruction ManagementCulinaryElectrical TechnicianFire ScienceHeating/CoolingTechnologyTradesSearch SchoolsADonlinembatoday.com is an advertising-supported site. Featured or trusted partner programs and all school search, finder, or match results are for schools that compensate us. This compensation does not influence our school rankings, resource guides, or other editorially-independent information published on this site.Got it!
Terms of Use and Privacy Policy for Use of OnlineMBAToday.com (Effective January 5, 2019)
Thank you for your interest and use of the content and services of OnlineMBAToday.com. This page will explain how OnlineMBAToday.com gathers and utilizes different kinds of information so that we may provide users with content, products, and services relevant to education options and related topics. By using our website, you are agreeing to this Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. Even when we obtain consent explicitly or implicitly, OnlineMBAToday.com's legitimate interest in obtaining data for its university and other education related clients is its legal basis for collecting data from persons in the European Union and countries with similar privacy laws.
OnlineMBAToday.com collects two kinds of information: submitted information and automatic information.
Automatic information includes certain types of anonymous information whenever you interact with OnlineMBAToday.com. This data aids in creating improvements in our user experience, such as providing more relevant and tailored content. For example, we use "cookies" to collect anonymous data for analytics, site optimization and for tailored advertising and marketing. This data includes (but is not limited to) your browser version, operating system version, and your IP address.
By utilizing our website, you acknowledge and agree that automatic information collected on OnlineMBAToday.com may be shared with schools, affiliated companies, and third parties for the purpose of providing information about degrees, programs and other education-related products and services.
Submitted information is data that is voluntarily inputted and submitted by users through our web forms, which may include personal contact information, such as name, telephone number, mailing address, and email address, as well as any other information that may be required to match users to an education product or service. Submitted information is collected, stored and shared with schools and other third parties as necessary to provide users with information about education-related services, in addition to schools and programs.
By submitting this information, you authorize OnlineMBAToday.com (as well as our affiliated schools and partners) to contact you in accordance with all applicable laws by phone, through text messages, or by email or mail regarding education options or related topics. You also acknowledge and agree that we retain the right to release any collected information, including personally identifiable information, as needed, to businesses providing our company with administration services (such as an email delivery service). In addition, through this action, you grant us, our affiliates, and our partners and vendors the right to contact you for a period of time, and relinquish any rights granted to you by the Do Not Call list or other applicable law. Your submission serves as an omission to Do Not Call requirements established by state and federal governments and may exempt us from other applicable laws.
If you receive any email communications from us, a school, or third party, you will be afforded the ability to unsubscribe through a link in the email, at which point you will be removed from further mailings from that sender.
We also retain the right to release your personal information in circumstances required by law, such as to abide by a subpoena or other legal procedure. This will be when, in good faith, we believe it is necessary to preserve our rights, ensure the safety of you or others, explore alleged fraud, to reply to a government or legal request, and/or in the instance that OnlineMBAToday.com is merging, acquisitioning, or selling some or all of its assets to a third party.
In addition, it is possible that we will revise our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy in the future if we change our practices. We recommend that you revisit this document periodically to stay up-to-date with our practices concerning your privacy and other important information.
Use of Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored in the user's web browser, including for technical purposes such as web analytics. By using this website, you acknowledge that we use cookies and consent to our use of cookies. Our web analytics are primarily performed using Google Analytics, a tool provided by Google, Inc.
Advertising cookies do not contain personally identifiable information and allow users to remain anonymous. However, they do permit advertisers to make ads more relevant to the user's interests. Advertising cookies are sometimes referred to as third-party cookies because they track navigation and publish ads on behalf of third parties. For more information about Google Analytics and its uses, check Google's privacy policy at https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245.
OnlineMBAToday.com, including services and partnerships with vendors and third-party service providers, may use cookies for Web analytics such as demographic and other anonymous data for web optimization and other analysis, and "lead auditing" to ensure the accuracy, relevance and validity of submitted information. In addition, our use of marketing and conversion-tracking cookies is for, but not limited to, targeting and optimizing digital ad serving to improve relevance, user experience, and advertising effectiveness.
You can remove cookies through your browser settings at any time, though you may need to do this on a per use and not one-time basis. You can also generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website.
Contact us if you have any questions or concerns about this Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, or if you wish to make a Subject Access Request under the General Data Protection Regulations of the European Union.
Primary Sidebar
Quick Degree FinderSelect a Degree LevelSelect a DegreeAssociate'sBachelor'sMaster'sDoctorateNon-Degree CoursesCertificate / DiplomaGraduate CertificatesSelect a CategorySelect a CategoryArt & DesignBusiness & ManagementComputers & TechnologyCriminal Justice & LegalEducation & TeachingLiberal Arts & HumanitiesNursing & HealthcarePsychology & CounselingScience & EngineeringTrades & CareersSelect a SubjectSelect a SubjectAnimationArt & Art HistoryCreative / DesignFashionFilmGame DesignGraphic DesignInterior DesignLandscape ArchitectureMultimedia DesignPhotographyVisual CommunicationsWeb DesignAccountingBusiness AdministrationBusiness IntelligenceEconomicsEntertainment ManagementEntrepreneurshipFinanceForensic AccountingHospitality ManagementHotel & Restaurant ManagementHuman ResourcesInternational BusinessInternet MarketingLogisticsManagementManagement Information SystemsMarketingNon-Profit ManagementOrganizational LeadershipProject ManagementPublic RelationsReal EstateRetail & Sales ManagementRisk ManagementSmall BusinessSports ManagementSupply Chain & LogisticsTaxationTraining & DevelopmentComputer EngineeringComputer ForensicsComputer ProgrammingComputer ScienceDatabase ManagementInformation Systems SecurityInformation TechnologyInternet SecurityMobile DevelopmentNetwork AdministrationNetwork SecuritySoftware EngineeringWeb DevelopmentCorrectionsCrime Scene InvestigationCriminal JusticeCriminologyCyber SecurityForensic ScienceHomeland SecurityLaw EnforcementLegal StudiesParalegalPublic Safety AdministrationAdult Education/LearningChild DevelopmentCoachingCurriculum & InstructionEarly Childhood EducationEducationEducational AdministrationEducational CounselingEducational LeadershipEducational TechnologyElementary EducationEnglish Language LearningHigher EducationK-12 EducationLibrary ScienceMath EducationMusic EducationOnline TeachingReading & LiteracySpecial EducationTeacher LicensureAnthropologyCommunicationsEnglishGeneral StudiesGeographyHistoryHuman & Family DevelopmentJournalismLiberal ArtsMedia CommunicationsMinistryMusicPolitical SciencePublic AdministrationPublic PolicySocial ScienceSocial WorkSociologyTheologyWritingDental AssistanceEmergency ManagementGerontologyHealth EducationHealth InformaticsHealth ScienceHealth ServicesHealthcare AdministrationHealthcare ManagementHuman ServicesMedical AssistingMedical CodingMedical Office AdministrationNurse Practitioner (RN Required)Nursing (RN required)Nursing Education (RN Required)Nutritional SciencesPharmacyPublic HealthRN to BSN (RN required)Sports MedicineSports Medicine/Physical TherapyVeterinaryX-Ray TechnicianAddictions & RecoveryBehavioral PsychologyChild and Adolescent PsychologyCounselingEducational PsychologyFamily CounselingForensic PsychologyOrganizational PsychologyPsychologyAeronautics/AviationBiomedical EngineeringCivil EngineeringDraftingElectronics EngineeringEngineeringEngineering ManagementEnvironmental ManagementEnvironmental ScienceIndustrial EngineeringMechanical EngineeringAutomotiveCarpentryConstruction ManagementCulinaryElectrical TechnicianFire ScienceHeating/CoolingTechnologyTradesSearch SchoolsADonlinembatoday.com is an advertising-supported site. Featured or trusted partner programs and all school search, finder, or match results are for schools that compensate us. This compensation does not influence our school rankings, resource guides, or other editorially-independent information published on this site.Got it!
Search This Site
Search this website
Featured Articles
The Top Business Trends That Will Drive Success
Top 100 Most Affordable Online MBA Programs
Top 25 Online MBA Specializations
Top 25 Fastest Online MBA Programs
Entrepreneurs and MBAs
Audrey McLaughlin, Kelley School of Business at Indiana University-Bloomington
Richard McNeal, Marylhurst University
Monica Boggan, Lamar University
Online MBA Director Interviews
An Interview with Pam Delany, Director of Graduate Admission and Recruitment of the W.P Carey School of Business at Arizona State University
An Interview with Kathy Farrell, Dean of the College of Business at the University of Nebraska, Lincoln
An Interview with Hasan Pirkul, Dean of the Naveen Jindal School of Business at the University of Texas at Dallas
An Interview with Raj Echambadi, the Dunton Family Dean of the D’Amore-McKim School of Business at Northeastern University
An Interview with Rosemary Hartigan and Ravi Mittal of the Graduate School of Business at the University of Maryland University College
An Interview with Jeff Tanner, Dean of the Strome College of Business at Old Dominion University
An Interview with Dr. Jun Zhao, Dean of the College of Business at Governors State University
An Interview with Dr. Gary Schirr, Director of the Online MBA Program at Radford University
An Interview with Jeffrey Brown, Dean and professor of Business for the Gies College of Business at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign
An Interview with Paul Russell, Director of Graduate Programs for the College of Business at East Carolina University
An Interview with Carly Broussard, Director of the MBA Program at Lamar University
An Interview with Elizabeth Rozell, Associate Dean and Director of the MBA Program for the College of Business at Missouri State University
Stacey Dorang Peeler, Managing Director of the Online MBA at Penn State University, Smeal College of Business
John Wells, Associate Dean at The University of Massachusetts Amherst, Isenberg School of Management
Erin Vincent, Indiana University-Bloomington
Jonathon Nichols, The University of Utah, David Eccles School of Business
An Interview with Michael Tarantino, Director of Recruitment & Admissions for Graduate Programs at Lehigh University
Employer Interviews
Derek Sciba of Crista Ministries
Resource Articles
Directory of Online MBA Programs in the U.S.
